好的 你已经完成了
All right, you're done.
让我们看一下答案
Let's take a look at the solution.
我们不能直接插入一个vector
While we cannot insert
a vector directly,
我们可以容易的把一个vector转为一个array
we can easily convert
a vector to an array.
一旦完成 BulkInsert方法将会高效的进行插入
Once we've done this, the BulkInsert
method will insert very efficiently.
如你所见 我们取消注释的下面的几行代码
As you can see, we've uncommented
out these next series of lines.
允许我们来测试输出来保证
This allows us to test our output,
to make sure
我们插入的数据是正确的
that we've actually inserted
the right thing into the database.
我们来允许我们的app
Let's actually run our app.
如你所见 我们实际上从数据库读出这些
And, as you can see, we're actually
reading the data out of the database
我们刚刚插入的全都正确的数据
that we just inserted all correctly.
现在 我们的后台将会有效的更新（数据） 但是我们
Now, our backend will
update efficiently, but we
我们需要一个方法来更新前台让其不在main UI线程中进行
really need a way to update the frontend
without doing it on the main UI thread.
现在 我们的后台将会有效的更新（数据） 但是我们
Now, our backend will update
efficiently, but we really need to be
查询一些东西在从网上查询他们之前
querying things before requesting
them from the internet.
总之 重点是有一个响应式的应用
After all, the point is to
have a responsive application.
我们仍没有更新屏幕直到在我们
We're still not even updating
the screen until after we've
从网络上拿到数据后
pulled data down from the web.
我们也想避免做在ui线程上做查询
We also want to avoid doing
our query on the UI thread.
因为 如果在UI线程上做查询类似的操作会引起Android
Because, doing operations like queries
on the UI thread cause Android not to be
不能尽快的绘制帧 从而引起帧率抖动(就是卡的意思)
able to draw frames fast enough,
which introduces frame rate jitter.
幸运的是 Adnroid提供了一个叫做Loaders的模式
Fortunately, Android offers
a pattern for that known as loaders.